let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1.,
        question: 'What is cuber security',
        answer: 'D. All of the mentioned',
        options: [
            'A. cuber security provides security against malware',
            'B. cyber security provides security against cyber attacks',
            'C. cyber security protects a system for cyber attacks',
            'D. All of the mentioned'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2.,
        question: 'Which of the following is defined as an attempt to steal,spy,damage or destroy computer systems, networks or their associated information?',
        answer: 'A. cyber attack',
        options: [
            'A. cyber attack',
            'B. computer security',
            'C. cryptography',
            'D. didgital hacking'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3.,
        question: 'Which of the following is a type of cyber security',
        answer: 'D. All of the above',
        options: [
            'A. Cloud attack',
            'B. network security',
            'C. appliction security',
            'D. All of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4.,
        question: 'What are the features of cyber security',
        answer: 'D. All of the above',
        options: [
            'A. compliance',
            'B. depense against internal threats',
            'C. threat prevention',
            'D. All of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5.,
        question: 'Which of the following is a stuxnet',
        answer: 'C. Worn',
        options: [
            'A. Trojan',
            'B. antivirus',
            'C. Worm',
            'D. virus'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6.,
        question: 'What is primary purpose of a firewall in cyberspace',
        answer: 'B. to prevent unathorized acces to a network',
        options: [
            'A. To block physical access to computer',
            'B. To prevent unathorized acces to network',
            'C. To enchance internet speed',
            'D. To encrypt data transmission'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7.,
        question: 'Which of the following can diminish the chance of data leakage',
        answer: 'A. Steganography',
        options: [
            'A. Steganography',
            'B. Chorography',
            'C. cryptography',
            'D. Authentication'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8.,
        question: 'What IOT collects?',
        answer: 'B. Machine generated data',
        options: [
            'A. Device data',
            'B. Machine generated data',
            'C. Sensor data',
            'D. Human generated data'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9.,
        question: 'Which of the following is a common cyber threat vector?',
        answer: 'B. trojan horse',
        options: [
            'A. Block chain',
            'B. torjan horse',
            'C. JPEG',
            'D. HTML'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10.,
        question: 'Which authentication method is more secure than WEP for Wi-fi networks?',
        answer: 'A. WPA2',
        options: [
            'A. WPA2',
            'B. MAC filtering',
            'C. WPA3',
            'D. WEP2'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11.,
        question: 'What is the primary purpose of WPA3 in wireless security?',
        answer: 'A. data encrption',
        options: [
            'A. data encrption',
            'B. network monitoring',
            'C. device pairing',
            'D. single boosting'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12.,
        question: 'What does SSID stand for for in the context of wireless network',
        answer: 'C. service set identifier',
        options: [
            'A. Secure server indentification',
            'B. system security identifier',
            'C. service set identifier',
            'D. singal strength indicator'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13.,
        question: ' Which of the following is not a steganography',
        answer: 'D. Burp suite',
        options: [
            'A. Crpture',
            'B. Steganographx plus',
            'C. rSteg',
            'D. Brup suite'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14.,
        question: 'What is the term for the practice of tricking indivisuals into divulging confidental information?',
        answer: 'C. phishing',
        options: [
            'A. Hacking',
            'B. Spoofing',
            'C. phishing',
            'D. Denial of service(Dos)'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15.,
        question: 'Which  security best practise involves using unique passwords for each accounts?',
        answer: 'D. password hygiene',
        options: [
            'A. Password sharing',
            'B. Password reuse',
            'C. password rotation',
            'D. password hygiene'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16.,
        question: 'Which of the following act violates cyber security?',
        answer: 'B. Attack',
        options: [
            'A. Exploit',
            'B. Attack',
            'C. Threat',
            'D. vulnerability'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17.,
        question: 'What is the main function of a firewall in a network security system?',
        answer: 'B. Access control',
        options: [
            'A. Encryption',
            'B. Access control',
            'C. intrusion detection',
            'D. virus scanning'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18.,
        question: 'Which of the following is an example of something you have in the control of 2FA?',
        answer: 'C. security token',
        options: [
            'A. password',
            'B. pin',
            'C. security token',
            'D. biometric data'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19.,
        question: 'Which disaster recovery phase invloves returning opreations to normal after disruption?',
        answer: 'D. recovery',
        options: [
            'A. Mitigation',
            'B. preparedeness',
            'C. respose',
            'D. recovery'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20.,
        question: 'Which key is used for creating a digital signature',
        answer: 'B. private key',
        options: [
            'A. public key',
            'B. private key',
            'C. session key',
            'D. symmetric key'
        ]
    }

] 